<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ebotics</string>
    <string name="home"></string>
    <string name="entre">How to be an entreprenuer</string>
    <string name="entera">Are you young, poor, unqualified – a student, or hating
        your job? Maybe a touch rebellious? Perfect.  You have no bad habits,

        and will work until your fingernails fall out and your eyeballs roll onto the desk.
        The world awaits you.Older, wiser, bit of money saved, experienced with a stable job?
        Maybe a mortgage and kids? Your job is much harder. It can be done, but it might feel
        like you’re trying to dance backwards through quicksand.

        The most important qualities of a good entrepreneur are energy and determination. It doesn’t hurt to be

        persuasive, but this can be learned. I started as a shy uber-nerd aged 21; I soon learned how to sell when
        it was the only way to feed myself.</string>

   <string name="entreb">Anyone who is thinking about becoming an entrepreneur should give it some serious thought and
        preparation first. You can’t just start up a new business on your own and hope that your approach to
        entrepreneurship will prove successful. A smart person who wants to become a business owner in her own right
        instead of working for someone else should take time to determine whether entrepreneurship is a logical step
        in the right direction. Some people are not capable of working on their own and some make better employees than
        employers. Becoming an entrepreneur requires significant forethought and evaluation before quitting your day job
        and investing time and money that you could easily lose. Below are seven basic steps that can move someone
        toward becoming an entrepreneur with a successful business.

        Be willing to take risks.
        Any startup business involves risks, the ultimate one, of course, being the possibility of failure. If you are
        uneasy about stepping out of your comfort zone, becoming an entrepreneur is probably not a good idea. For one
        thing, you could spend all your extra time (assuming you still hold a full-time job doing something else) trying
        to get your own business off the ground, only to have it fall flat. You are likely to hit a few glitches along
        the way, even if the business begins to take off. You might struggle to get enough customers or the right kind
        of customers. It’s not easy balancing the various facets of running your own business, from marketing,
        production, quality control, delivery, and accounting. You will have to develop a certain amount of expertise
        in all these areas or be able to hire others who know what to do.</string>

    <style name="DefaultButtonText">
        <item name="android:layout_width">fill_parent</item>
        <item name="android:layout_height">wrap_content</item>
        <item name="android:textColor">#ffffff</item>
        <item name="android:gravity">center</item>
        <item name="android:layout_margin">3dp</item>
        <item name="android:textStyle">normal</item>
        <item name="android:textSize">20sp</item>
        <item name="android:shadowColor">#f9f9f9</item>
        <item name="android:shadowDx">1</item>
        <item name="android:shadowDy">1</item>
        <item name="android:shadowRadius">1</item>
    </style>
    
    <!--Robotics page-->

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="one_string">One</string>
    <string name="two_string">Two</string>
    <string name="three_string">Three</string>
    <string name="four_string">Four</string>

</resources>
